Welcome to On the Brink. My name is Henry Harris and I'm an investor with Castle Isle Inventures.
Today on the show, I'm joined by Corn from Urine Finance. Urine Finance has been building
DeFi infrastructure and providing verifiable risk-adjusted yield strategies since 2020.
Corn and I discussed how DeFi has evolved since the collapse of Terraluna in 2022
and how recent volatility in the market once again highlighted the need for proper risk
management and transparency in DeFi. We also touched on the state of cybersecurity for
on-chain products as well as what it's going to take to get non-crypto-native institutions
comfortable interacting with DeFi. Without further ado, here's my conversation with Corn from Urine
Finance. Matt Walsh and Nick Carter are partners at Castle Isle Inventures. All of these expressed
by them or the guests on this podcast are solely their opinions and do not reflect the
opinions of Castle Isle Inventures. Guests and hosts may maintain positions in the assets discussed
in this podcast. You should not treat any opinion expressed by anyone on this podcast
as a specific inducement to make a particular investment or follow a particular strategy,
but only as an expression of their personal opinion. This podcast is for informational purposes only.
Thank you for inviting me. This is
Pulpy Taco's favorite podcast, so I could not miss it. I only attend the really high signal stuff.
Today is a state of the union on decentralized finance on DeFi and maybe just a level set
your background, just how you got into crypto and DeFi and we can go from there.
I have been in crypto full-time since November of 2021, so if you remember back then, that was
the top of the top in the past four years. I had been following crypto for a long time and
I was working with Cisco Network's largest partner for 10 years in the data center space,
building networks and data centers for hospitals. Someone from YERN was in a telegram chat with
me and they knew that I did a lot of technical selling and the IT space was starting to slow
down because especially in healthcare, every time someone deployed Epic for their medical record
system, they had to go and buy a ton of hardware. Upgrading to Epic was definitely their biggest
capital expense like the hospital ever goes through. Epic made the transition to be a web app.
The customers don't need to buy storage and area networks. They don't need to buy all new
Cisco switching and stuff like that, so I saw it space starting to slow down and
getting involved with YERN back then, we had over $6 billion of deposits. We were
in the top five for our D5 projects and we had 125 contributors, I think back then.
It was a big project and there was no way that I was going to say no to that opportunity, so
I took it and I'm still doing BD for YERN today. I'm responsible for all of the
customer experiences that we have. We have a B2B approach still. We want to get people to
build on top of YERN vaults and consume the tokenized strategies that we have. If people are not
getting answers really fast, they feel unsupported. They'll go to one of the other 9 million vault
projects out there. My responsibility is to make sure that they're happy, make sure they're coming
in the door. We get a lot of inbound requests for strategies to be made still because they know
that if they get a YERN strategy made, someone from the YERN security team is going to have to do
diligence on it. They're going to have to do at least something of like a light audit on the code
base and make sure that it's safe. It's my job to also qualify those opportunities because there
are a lot of them and I can't bring every single one of them to the curation or like security team
to that. I have to make sure that they've gone through my filter before I pass it on to them.
Those come in all the time for strategies, for collaterals, for our curation arm. It's always
been busy ever since I joined four years ago. Even if we're not churning out all these strategies,
we're definitely evaluating them. Customer support is something of an unsolved problem
within the crypto world. Who do you call when you're dealing with a decentralized protocol?
It's good to know that you're on the other end picking up the phone. In terms of the history
of YERN, you mentioned starting back in 2021, it was to my knowledge, it was around even before
then. What's the history of DeFi protocols and how they've evolved through 2021 and all the craziness
and then maybe all the way up to today in your experience?
Back when I started and we had 120 contributors, we had this mantra that YERN was very open and
anyone could join. To be honest, we still have that same culture today. One of the people who
actually went on to build YERN Vault V3 Schlag, we came across him in a hackathon, I think it was.
He submitted a strategy that he created and we thought that he was a former YERN contributor.
It was so perfect. We had 50 other people who had made strategies and every single one of them
was very low quality. The truth is today, if you build something on YERN and we think it's really
good, we will seriously consider hiring you. But we had to be more selective about who we're
onboarding as time went on. The bar kept getting higher and higher and that's a really good thing.
We started out that way back then. When I first joined, we had all this money, we were making
$100 million in profits in 2021, I think it was. Then the first thing that happened was
UST. The yields were 20%. Everyone was like, you got to make a strategy for a UST or you're
going to lose deposits. Guess what? We started losing a ton of deposits and we refused to make a
strategy for it because it was not a structurally sound project. We knew that something was going
to happen. We knew that it was a bit of a Ponzi. How did you figure that out? Just for context,
UST, Terra Luna collapsed, ended up losing tens of billions of dollars. Doquan was the CEO.
But how did you guys in the moment see through that? Anytime a stable is backed by a governance token,
it's not going to end well. It's impossible. The governance token is going to go to zero at some
point. Whether the market likes it or not, there is no way of avoiding it. We saw that happening.
It just was best for us to not play a part in that and just see our vaults just leak value
to go to other places. At the same time, that is also when the risk-free rate, when treasury rates
started to go up. There was a pending bear market. It was definitely on the way. We saw that DeFi
yields started to go down. The way that we get most of our yields is from supplying to lending
markets. When people are not borrowing, the yields are going to go down. What happened was we started
to lose even more TBL for people going and wanting to get that risk-free rate. It's understandable,
100%. Yarn, however, was not going to bend in our culture, in our values. We were not going to start
onboarding risky RWA yields. We need to have everything on chain. That's how it is for us.
We need everything to be verifiable. This was also a significant headwind coming into 2022 for us.
Very taking a step back when we talk about strategies and vaults and people were clamoring
for UST vaults. Essentially, what people are asking for here is they have a stable coin or
maybe they have Ethereum on chain. They want to put it to work somehow and they want to turn
that into a yield-bearing asset. What Yarn does is almost like a portfolio manager, so to speak,
curates these strategies that involve other DeFi protocols, maybe infrastructure that
Yarn's built, maybe infrastructure that Aave or Morpho or other lending protocols have built
and in a risk-managed way, derive a structured product on chain. Maybe you could say that
gives the end user a yield for their stable coin that they started with. Is that the right way to
think about it? Exactly. There are a list of prerequisites that we need to make sure are checked
before we go and build a strategy for something. Yes, the idea is that we have a multi-strategy
vault. Say we have a vault for USDC, we go and deposit that USDC into a bunch of different
lending markets today like Fluid and Morpho and Aave and wherever else. We rebalance all of those
strategies every hour depending on where the best APY is.
Terra collapse is 2022. We entered a bear market both with respect to token prices and just general
value that's locked in DeFi protocols. We start to come out of that into late 2023-2024 and
into this year. Take me maybe up to date to the current state of DeFi vaults within them,
then we can start to talk about the events of about a month ago, October 10th. There was this
mass liquidation event across crypto and in the past week or two, some bodies have started to
float to shore within DeFi on the higher risk end of the spectrum when it comes to vault management
and tokenization. Back a couple of years ago, like you said 2023-2024, it was like the depths of
the bear market. It was very quiet. A lot of the developers that we were working on in crypto,
some of them left, some of them went on to go back to doing what they were doing or start other new
projects. I think it was a talent drain. As I was trying to get people to build on top of your
vaults, I was getting the feedback that what you built, your vault v3 is clunky, hard to use,
difficult to understand. But truth be told, it is because everything that we were doing is
programmatic and on-chain and you have to be a pretty good developer to bring something to market
that's not going to get hacked. Some folks decided to make an easy button for vaults and that easy
button is turning your vault into a multi-sig. Basically, you have this product where all of
this capital flows into and you have a bunch of different people who can decide to build transactions
to send your money wherever they want, whenever they want. This is banking but worse, basically.
That's our perspective on it because this gives people the opportunity to still be anonymous,
but to also have full control over your funds and for you to have no visibility into the decisions
that are going on or even where your funds are going to be going to if they're going to deposit
those into a black box, like a centralized exchange or something like that. There's a lot of structural
issues with those multi-sig-fied projects. Even more so, they were able to align stakeholders
better than we were. Originally, when Yeren took off, everybody knows about Wifey Token.
That's Andre's baby. Yeren was the first fair launch project. What that meant was people could
farm Wifey Token. I was working on this project. Now it's called Katana Chain,
Polygon Broad to Market along with us. Last year in 2024, I was going around and talking to a lot
of VCs and look at funds about coming on board Katana with us. It was a really good experience
for me to jog my memory and just see how many people were involved in Yeren. Way back then,
these VCs, a lot of them still say, we got into crypto because of Yeren. Yeren was one of the
projects that we invested our time and focused in way back then. That meant that they had Wifey
Token. They had stake in our success. When the bear market came, token prices went down,
they dumped their bags. Yeren does not have a token print. We have a finite amount of tokens.
Those are the incentives that these new multi-sig projects started to bring to the table and started
doing raises. Now you have these liquid funds and VCs more aligned with the success of those
products compared to using Yeren. This is headwind number three that started to hit us and
we're still experiencing that right now. It's hard to think about this problem because
is someone going to come to market with a new competitor every single time and reload the
incentives? The mercenary money is just going to float into that new project. Is this going to be
the cycle forever? There's this finite amount of capital within DeFi. If my option as an allocator
is, okay, I can get 8% maybe from this Yeren vault with no token rewards on top of it,
or I can get 12% from these riskier strategies on this newer vault. On top of that, maybe an
additional 5% to 10% of APY from this token that they're a newer protocol so they have a newer
token and they're giving it out to people as incentives. That's not necessarily a Web3
native idea. Every time I open my Lyft app, there's some new reason why they're going to pay me $5
to use Lyft instead of go to Uber, but it's just more invasive. It feels like within crypto.
That's what is happening here. You have these things that are somewhere between what you say
opaque banking opportunities and unregulated hedge funds where people were depositing their
stablecoins into a black box for a group of three people that were claiming to be a DeFi protocol
to just go and loop into risky strategies. The way those strategies would be represented on the
market is in a token. Let's use one of these tokens that has recently blown up in the last
couple of weeks, XUSD. One of the problems with a lot of these is that the value of them gets
pegged to a dollar and they sort of rebase the yield on top of it. If it's a 20% APY strategy,
it'll start at $1 and the value of that token will grow as the yield accrues to it.
Even if these protocols aren't calling their product a stablecoin, so to speak, just by
including the letters USD in the name or pegging it to a dollar, I think sometimes it gives users
probably a false sense of security that what they're putting their money into is not volatile or not
risky. Really under the hood, there are risky things happening. What we saw with XUSD, I guess,
you'll have better info on this than me, is that the value of the token completely collapsed once
people realized that the curators or the managers of this protocol had lost a lot of the money.
So what kind of happened there? This all started for us back in May. There were a bunch of people
shilling this new project. We took a look at it. We had actually talked to them previously
the year before about doing some real-world asset strategies with them and it didn't end up working
and then we saw that they had this vault and we found their debank and we looked at the TVL
that it had versus the TVL that they were displaying on their site. We saw that it did not match up.
We asked them why and they said at the time that they were depositing into hyper liquid some sort
of carry trade strategy. At that point, we would definitely not touch it. It is a black box and
we said to them, this is super risky. You can't just have people trusting that there is backing
to this when you cannot prove it at all. They ended up copying and pasting those private messages
and posting them in their Discord and dunking on me over and over back in May. I did not appreciate
that. But you're not better. Let the record show that you're not better about it.
I kind of forgot about it until a few months ago when they started to get even more deposits.
I realized that they had tapped into the yields and more Discord, which is like a farming group
that's been around for a number of years. After all of those liquidations happened on 1010,
Schlag and the rest of the Yarn security team found on chain that a lot of these projects and
funds had some losses. To us, there was no way that everyone from stream finance got out of
those strategies without taking losses. We knew that there was a hole there. There just had to be.
Schlag started digging more into the on chain data, found all of this daisy chain of looping,
recursive lending, and curators offering up liquidity from user deposits in order to fuel
all of this. We found that even though they had grown from $160 million of deposits into $500
million, there were really no net new deposits coming in. This was just a scheme going on
the back end. When we asked them about it, there was no proof of anything. Nothing that they were
doing was verifiable. It's just a huge red flag. Truth be told, if this all did not happen on 1010,
if this ball didn't get started rolling, they would still be looping more right now. They would
still be accepting user deposits right now, knowing that they had a hole they had to have known
on the back end. It would have just kept on getting bigger and bigger and bigger.
I'm glad that things shook out the way they did. It was not an easy few weeks to deal with all this
stuff, but here we are. What ends up happening is that you have this tokenized strategy, XUSD,
that gets involved in other vaults. XUSD itself is a tokenized vault, so to speak,
that's investing in DeFi protocols to get the yield, but then that representation of DeFi yield
gets placed into another vault, a vault of vaults. Those vaults then lose value because
they have invested in XUSD, which has de-pegged and lost its value. We've talked about curators a
little bit here. Maybe if you could unpack that term, what's the role of a risk curator in DeFi?
You have the people depositing. On one side, you have the DeFi protocols on the other side,
where the actual lending and borrowing happens. Then in the middle, there's these actors that
are putting together these vaults. They also live directly on some of these protocols like
Euler and Morpho and set the parameters of, you want to borrow against this asset,
we deem this asset to be risk averse enough that you can borrow at a 95% LTV instead of
an 85% LTV. What's the role and maybe the faults of the risk curators in some of these scenarios?
There are a lot of curators these days, and there are a lot of vault projects these days.
I don't really know why because none of us are making any money. I just want that to be clear.
This is not a great business. You have to have billions of dollars in deposits
to generate the amount of revenue Abe is making or any of these other really big projects right
now. Being a curator is not a terribly good business. Right now, for a lot of stuff that we
do, we even have fees turned off because it just doesn't matter. We want to have competitive rates,
and the profits that we bring in the door are just really small. It's our job as a curator to
make sure that we're using sound collateral that matches the risk that people assume is going on
in that vault. We also need to make sure that we have good automation, that things are being
replenished when they need to. If there's borrowers who have a big appetite, we need to make sure that
there's liquidity in that vault for them to borrow. We need to understand the interest rate
curves. We need to make sure that we're being reactive to everything in the market. There's a
lot of work that has to be done. We also have to meet the needs of demand for people offering up new
collaterals or wanting to borrow in the first place. We need to make sure that there's enough
deposits. What you're doing right now is we have this parent level vault, and this goes into
deposits into all of these different lending markets. Even as a curator, we can pull money
from YVUSDC and throw it into something that we're curating on Morfo if it needs liquidity.
We have a multi-tiered business where not every curator has that open to them right now.
We want to discourage degenerate recursive looping. We want to make sure that everything that we're
doing is really safe. To us, reputation is everything. We're completely blind to accepting
short-term incentives. We don't do any side deals or anything like that. Whenever people
ask us to build products that just farm points, we usually say no. Because we know that the amount
of work that goes into building and supporting strategies is probably not going to be worth the
effort in fees or deposits. There's a lot of stuff that we say no to. I think it just makes our
ability to make it through tough economic conditions that much more strong. Survival is
everything. It's pretty clear to us now that some curators are going to take big risks and they're
going to damage their reputation. We'll be here to survive and to be strong and safe and get those
deposits when people eventually come back into DeFi because they will. In the long run, usually
good risk management pays off. It's not just in DeFi where people blow themselves chasing higher
returns everywhere in finance. Switching gears a little bit, curious as someone who's building in
DeFi, from your perspective, what's the state of on-chain cybersecurity right now? Recently,
Balancer, which is a decentralized swapping exchange similar to Uniswap, was just hacked for
over $100 million GMX earlier this year, a decentralized perpetual protocol similar to
Hyperliquid. Both have been around since 2020, probably before. I think it was also hacked for
a significant amount. I think those two especially caught people off guard of no one's safe. There's
this idea and cryptoness of lendiness where, okay, something's been around for four, five,
six years. I feel safe putting my money in this protocol and Balancer and GMX broke that model
a little bit. A lot of these protocols, they tout their audits that they've done,
they tout the security partners that they're working with, our code is safe, but are those
tools enough? What else needs to exist to stop another Balancer from happening?
I don't want to spook people, but the reality is low-risk DeFi is not here yet.
Low-risk DeFi and italics vision of that is great. I have no doubt that time in the market
will get us there. Is the five years of DeFi as whole lifetime enough for that to happen so far?
Apparently, it's not. The best that we can do today is verifiable DeFi. Being able to see
everything that's going on on chain and verify it to know that it's real.
One of the things I did with Yarn also is I started an audit company. It's called Electisec
right now, formerly YAudit and Y Academy. We're actually changing the name back to YAudit pretty
soon. From this experience, I can say that code quality has definitely gone up. No question.
The amount of safety that teams are taking into account right now is not slowing down.
I think we've done 17 engagements with Oiler. They're not taking their foot off the gas for
security. They're always going to be auditing their code bases. This is a time in the market thing.
For code that is immutable, where you don't really know where the dangers could be,
people need to just build their code as simply as possible, leave out tons of complexity where
they can, and that's going to help reduce the amount of vulnerabilities. Also,
security is a journey. Just because you launch your code base does not mean that there are no
vulnerabilities in it. Just because you've been in the market for a year doesn't mean that there's
anything wrong with it. Do contests have big meaningful bug bounties? Yarn has paid out bug
bounties before for stuff that people have caught. It's worked out well. Participating in bug bounties
works, so do it. I think the combination of all these things and a layered security approach,
along with time in the market, will get us the safety that we need for Glowisk DeFi, but it's
going to take constant improvement for a long time. A Swiss cheese approach, I guess, multiple layers
that cover up the holes. What are the implications of all this on not only the traditional finance
world's appetite for investing in exploring DeFi, but just kind of an everyday, non-crypto-native
person that says, well, I could get 3.5%, 4% right now for my savings account, or I could get
maybe 7%, 8%, 10% of safe, quote unquote, crypto-native DeFi yield. But given this risk of
unregulated black box hedge funds out there acting as tokens, given this risk of a hack to the protocol,
is that increase from the risk-free government treasury rate enough to make DeFi interesting
to people outside of crypto? I was in New York City last week to meet with a bunch of
traditional finance companies, and to be very honest, they're spooked about it.
The difference between 3.5% and 5% is not enough for them to come into DeFi. It's going to take
some time to build back the reputation and make sure that things are safe again. I was very surprised
that some of the people who I met with are new to crypto. They're representing their companies,
push for DeFi products. They don't understand the difference between multi-sigfi and
programmatic vaults. It's something that I've had to explain to them. I'm totally happy to do it.
I want to do it more, but I need to convince them that there is a big difference. And just because
you can manipulate your vault share price, that is not a good thing in many cases.
Having full control over that also brings an additional risk into the equation.
It's really good that talent and attention is coming into crypto from that side of the fence.
I don't think that's going to stop, but they're very hesitant to use true verifiable DeFi, for
sure. Do you think there's any inverse correlation of demand for DeFi products as the government
treasury rate comes down? Rates are starting to come down. You mentioned that Terra, Luna,
Collapse happened to line up with rates rocketing up to 5%. Is that bullish for DeFi or will yields
come down in DeFi the same way that they're going to come down outside of crypto?
If the risk-free rate comes down, it is unquestionably bullish for DeFi. Deposits will come back
in the door. If the risk-free rate is 1% or 2% and we're doing 6%, 7%, or 8%, they will come into
DeFi. I have no doubt in my mind about that. Shout out to Ron Powell, if you're listening.
How do you think all this impacts a crypto investor or retail investor's willingness
to invest in the native tokens of these DeFi protocols? You mentioned,
a token, all of these newer multi-sig 5 protocols even have tokens too. How should
people think about valuing those, especially once they're in their post-incentive phase
of their lifecycle? How do you guys think about driving value to people that want to hold the
year in token? There are two ways of building value into governance tokens these days, aside
from just having it to vote in your favor for things that you want to see happen,
buy and burn, or distributing profits through your token. Those are the two paths that people can
take. Yarn does not see the value in just buying and burning tokens. What we're choosing to do is
rebuild Wi-Fi as a still locking it to get a distribution of profits, but doing a more
short-term lock. That's what we're going to be doing right now. I think it's a one-month lock
period. Then you get a share of all the profits that we are going to be distributing.
This is the time that Yarn has to go and turn the fee switch on too. We're more focused on
generating profits than we once were. That's good to hear. Generating profits for a long time
didn't seem to be the focus for many people in crypto. In the last year, there's definitely been
in this newer SUC environment, while not everything is clear, we're still in a pre-clarity era,
so to speak, for which of these things are securities and which of them are. You still
have to give people reasons to hold these tokens for the long term, rather not to just think of
them as points or air miles that you can receive and spend right away. The meta recently has been
for vaults projects to be pre-deposit vaults for new alt-thus and stuff they're launching.
That is a really short-term thing. You get the money in the door, but then within a few months,
it might not be there. Profits that are generated from those events are not going to be as significant
as getting user adoption for people who want to use your strategies long term as a high-quality
source of yield. We worked for a long time on the Katana L2. Polygon was not the only group who
was evaluating using yarn vaults as pre-deposit vaults. They were the only group to pick yarn
as their pre-deposit vault, though. The reason why is because David Silverman and Mark Boyron
over at Polygon fully understood the risk of using a multi-sig where price per share could be
manipulated. They wanted to do stuff that was fully on-chain. I love them for that. We ended up
doubling our TBL this year because of that. Yarn vaults are deeply embedded into Katana chain.
It's just been a real pleasure to work with people in DeFi who really align with our own values of
safety and being verifiable. A lot of this is going to come down to education to a certain extent,
especially going back to your conversation with those finance folks in New York of like,
here's why this matters. Here's why you want these assets to be verifiably on-chain, not just in some
black box, even if you might get 100, 200 bibs lower yield. You're paying for that on a risk
reward spectrum. You're right. People don't understand that. Here's a good example. If
you're in just a stake-deep position or like an LRT and you're earning yield that slightly outperforms
our own Weh1 vault, first of all, as the price of beef goes up, the withdrawal queue is not going
to go down. It's only going to get longer. If you're also faced to exit your position at a time
when those pools are unbalanced, you could wipe out six months or a year of your yield instantly.
If you're using a year-in-vault, it's always liquid all the time and it's a cash-equivalent
product. Even though your yield will be slightly less, you will get to keep it. People don't seem
to really understand that yet, but part of my discovery in New York last week talking to some
of these traditional finance firms and hedge funds is that there is an audience for a cash-equivalent
yield-bearing product. It is the director of a treasury. They could be the director of treasury
of like a hospital or a university, a pension, but they need to earn yield on their deposits,
but also have them be liquid all the time. They might have their CFO ask them,
you need to liquidate this because we need to go and make a payment for something by a building.
If they can exit that position that they were earning yield on without losing that yield or
without taking on additional risk and being able to do it whenever they want, if your time in the
vault is unpredictable, you're involved to the product that you should be using. You should be
using something that is cash-equivalent. I got my hands on this huge database of all these treasury
managers and I'm going to give it a shot of going down and seeing who has an appetite to at least
learn about what verifiable DeFi is and what we're bringing to the table. I'm not expecting to get
a huge amount of yeses, but even getting a few and making those connections is where we need to
start. Knocking on doors, spreading the good word, someone's got to do it. Exactly. It's not going
to be easy. Another thing underlying a lot of this conversation is everything exists in crypto
on a spectrum of centralized to decentralized. DeFi, decentralized finance, even within DeFi,
a lot of these things, certainly, I wouldn't call them to be decentralized. It's kind of
decentralized and name only, especially when we talk about these multi-sig-fi products, these
on-chain, off-chain hedge funds where it's just a couple of guys yoloing your positions into high
risk yield. Where do you think we are today on this spectrum of centralization to decentralization
within DeFi and crypto, and are we headed in the right direction, especially as more
triad-fi people come on chains, more payments move to stablecoins? A lot of people, DeFi purists,
even will stick their noses up at stablecoins sometimes as USDC may be on Ethereum, on a
decentralized blockchain, but you're still trusting, circle the company to mint you the USDC and buy
and custody the treasury asset that's underlying it and redeem it when you ask for it. There's still
a level of trust involved there. Where are we on that spectrum? Are we headed in the right
direction in your opinion? There's a good mix of signals in there, to be honest, but if you zoom
out, I think we are trending in the right direction. The reason why I say that is just because I've
seen TVL start to leave some of these projects that are in DeFi, but are reliant on these
centralized exchanges or parties or whatever, reducing counterparty risk and relying on maybe
something that is just a smart contract, getting the human element out of decision making will
become more popular over time in certain circles. There's always going to be people who will prefer
the USDC because it is backed by the government of somewhere or the bank is backed by the government.
I think that that product will always be out there for a good reason, too. At least for Ethereum's
vision, low risk DeFi is a great North Star and that does not involve these centralized entities
in that equation at all. It just establishes a base rate of yield. Even these centralized parties
will sometimes fall back on that. For instance, I think at the peak TVL of Athena,
only 30% of their funds were in the carry trade strategy going on between all these centralized
exchanges. The rest of it went into Aave to get the Aave yield, which is exactly what we do.
You need a base rate of yield, and if it's there and it's robust, can take giant deposits,
and people are definitely going to use it. That's good. We're moving in the right direction.
People are learning. We're educating people. Maybe that's a good place to leave it.
Corn, thanks so much for coming on. Appreciate the time. We should do it again soon.
Yeah, we should. Thank you for having me. Let me know if you ever have any questions
anybody listening. I'm always around. Thanks for listening to another episode of
On the Brink with Castle Island. To learn more about Castle Island, visit castleisland.tc.
And to listen to all of our podcast episodes, please visit castleisland.tc.com or just click
on the tab on our website. Thanks for listening.